

# Jennifer L. Brown

811 Calais Street, Bellevue, NE 68123 Home: 816-536-4349 Cell: 816-536-4349 jennifer.l.brown79@gmail.com

#### **Career Overview**

A Web Designer and Developer experienced in the field of web programming, with skills in designing, development optimization of web applications and 12 years of experience in Information Technology/Security, Network Administration, Internet Security, Client Support Administration, and more.

### **Qualifications**

- Web Content Management
- Database Servers
- Technical Help Desk Experience
- Information Security
- · GUI and Tools
- Excellent Problem Solving Skills

- Strong Analytical Skills
- Proficiency in TCP/IP Protocols
- Project Management
- Document Management
- Development and Design Principles of Process

#### **Professional Skills**

- JavaScript, jQuery
  - ActionScript, FLEX, Flash
  - PHP, MvSQL
  - XHTML, HTML, HTML5
  - CSS, CSS3
  - DOM, FlashLite

- Python, Node.js, AngularJS
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Object Oriented Programming
- Responsive Web Design
- App Development
- Microsoft Operating Suite

- XML, API
- GIT
- Interface Design and Structure
- Digital Video and Audio CODECs
- MAMP

## **Experience**

Student, Full Sail University, Winter Park, FL

Web Design and Development

United States Air Force, Strategic Air Command (STRATCOM), Offutt AFB, Nebraska

Knowledge Operations Management Craftsman

United States Air Force, Air Combat Command (ACC), Whiteman AFB, Missouri

Information Management Specialist

United States Air Force, Technical School (TS), Biloxi, Mississippi United States Air Force, Basic Military Training (BMT), Lackland AFB, Texas

June 2012 – June 2014

October 2009 – June 2012

January 2000 – October 2009

October 1999 – December 1999 August 1999 – October 1999

#### Education

Full Sail University
Bachelor of Science: Web Design and Development

Winter Park, Florida, USA

June 2014

### **Accomplishments/Awards**

2014 Web Design and Development Advanced Achievement Award Joint Service Commendation Medal, STRATCOM, USAF Air Force Commendation Medal, ACC, USAF

June 2014 August 2011 October 2008